const questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "How long would it take to watch all of Game of Thrones, in minutes?",
        answer: 3810
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "How many starting quarterbacks has the Cleveland Browns had?",
        answer: 63
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "How many people were employed in the rubber industry in Akron at its peak?",
        answer: 85000
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "How many ping pong balls can fit in a C-5 Galaxy airplane (largest airplane in the US Air Force industry)?",
        answer: 25000000
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "How many words can be made out of the word Dalmatian?",
        answer: 130
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "How far away is Akron, CO from Akron, OH, in miles?",
        answer: 1265
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "How many pounds of fries does McDonaldâ€™s sell globally per day?",
        answer: 9000000
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "What is the distance in yards from the surface of the Earth to the surface of the Moon?",
        answer: 420388233
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "How many sheets of paper are in one pound?",
        answer: 500
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "In LaMans France they host a 24-hour race. Teams are formed to race cars for 24 hours. How many kilometers were covered by the fastest team in 24 hours?",
        answer: 4968
    },
    {
        number: 11,
        question: "How many seeds does a giant sunflower make?",
        answer: 1080
    },
    {
        number: 12,
        question: "What is the volume of Lake Erie in cubic miles?",
        answer: 115
    },
    {
        number: 13,
        question: "What is the surface area of a baseball in square centimeters?",
        answer: 174
    }
  ];
  
  export default questions;